嘿，欢迎回到这个关于ASP.NET Core的视频
Hey there, welcome back to this video about ASP.NET Core
我叫Jeff Fritz，我是Jon Galloway
my name is Jeff Fritz, I'm Jon Galloway
我们在这些视频中讨论了很多关于构建新应用的视频
and we've been talking a lot in these videos about building new applications and
我们可以用它们做什么，然后我们就开始讨论生产和不同的环境。
what we can do with them ，and then we even got into talking a little bit about production and different environments.
我如何做呢？
How do I host this ?
把它发布出来，放到一个生产环境 Jon
actually publish it and put it somewhere in a production space Jon.
是的，这是一个很好的问题
yeah so it's a great question and it's
这里面有很多信息，比如细微差别，对吧？
it's there's a lot of information a lot of  it， like nuances to this ，right？
部署变得更加复杂了
deploying ，deploying has gotten a little more complicated because
ASP.NE Core到处运行
ASP.NET Core runs everywhere
是的，
yeah,
所以你必须考虑，
so you have to think about,
你知道，
you know,
你的应用程序是如何托管的
how is your application actually hosted
你怎么知道你把它部署到什么地方
and how are you know where you are deploying it to in the
你可以部署地方之间的细微差别
slight differences between the places you can deploy to
好的。
ok.
首先
so to start with
我们要讨论的是如何托管ASP.NET Core
we're going to talk about actually hosting  ASP.NET Core
这里有个有趣的地方
and you know an interesting thing here
ASP.NET Core实际上是用Kestrel托管的。
ASP.NET Core is actually hosted using Kestrel.
Kestrel是一个轻量级的web服务器包
and Kestrel is a lightweight web server package
它实际上是一个我添加到应用程序的NuGet包
it's actually a NuGet package that I add my application
这样就可以打开HTTP服务了。
that kind of turns on HTTP serving.
好的，所以我管理运行在我的应用程序内部的HTTP服务器。
OK, so I manage HTTP server that lives inside of my application.
所以，对任何环境来说都是很常见
So, the kind of the common things to any environment is
你会设置一个主机，
you'll set up a host,
然后一旦你把你的应用发布到一个文件夹，
and then once you on your publish  you know your application to a folder on there,
你会看到你会有一个进程管理器
you'll see that you'll have a process manager
这将确保我的应用程序继续运行
that's going to make sure that my application continues running
然后我将会有一个反向代理它会把流量发送给我。
And then I'm going to have a reverse proxy that's going to send the traffic back to me.
好的
okay
所以关于你的整个事情
so that whole thing about  you know
我是如何发布的，我的应用程序是如何托管的，
how I'm actually publishing and I'm how my application is hosting itself is,
这是用kestrel完成的
this is done using kestrel
为了看到这个动作我们来看看一个默认的项目
so to see this in action let's take a look at a default project
这只是文件名项目
this is just file name project
明白吗？
okay ?
我有
and I've got
如果我看我的NuGet包，
if I look in my NuGet packages,
我有一个AspNetCoreAll meta包。
I've got the AspNetCoreAll meta package.
当然
Sure
如果我把它展开在这个列表.在某个地方有Kestrel，所以如果我——
And if I expand this out somewhere in that list  we've got Kestrel. so if I--
所以你实际上不需要在你的应用程序中安装kestrel
so you actually don't need to install kestrel in your application
默认情况下，新web将启用Kestrel
File New web is going to have Kestrel enabled by default
对的
right
因为这个包包含了aspnetcore，所有的元数据包
because that package is included AspNetCore.All meta package
所有东西都在这。
verything in the kitchen-sink.
是的，
yep,
实际上我可以创建一个控制台应用程序，
and I could actually just create a console application,
然后加上这个Kestrel包
and then add this Kestrel package
我的应用程序现在是一个网页应用
and my application is now a web app
很好
oh cool right
这很简洁。
so that's pretty neat.
所以如果我们
so if we if we
如果我们看下我们的Startup
if we hop back out of there and we look at our Startup,
不好意思
so excuse me are
我们的program CS
our program CS.
我们得到的是实际运行的Kestrel
what we've got here is  the actual spinning up Kestrel
并且，你提到了你可以启动一个控制台应用程序并将web服务器添加给它。
and； you mentioned if you could start a console application and  add the web server to it.
对于控制台应用程序来说，这看起来像是一个正常的静态void
this looks like a normal static void mean for a console application
完全是
it completely is
没有任何花招，这是一个控制台应用
No trickery at all this is literally a console app
添加了一些额外的NuGet包
that has some additional NuGet packages added
正因为如此，
and because of that,
我们得到Microsoft ASPNetCore Hosting
we've got Microsoft ASPNetCore Hosting
这就可以运行Kestrel并托管我们的应用程序，
and that's able to run Kestrel and host our application，cool
在Asp.NetCore2,之前的版本中
so in previous releases before Asp.NetCore2,
这里有更多的代码，
there was a lot more code in here,
这几乎是一种样板
And it was pretty much boilerplate
你总是做同样的事情，你总是说在这里使用——
you always did the same things，you always said here use--
你知道，使用这些环境设置，然后做这个。
you know, use these environment settings and do this and do that.
所以他们所做的我喜欢这个，这对我来说是非常简单的
so what they've done and I like this it's definitely simplified things quite a bit for me is
他们有一个默认的web主机构建器，你会在这里看到web主机创建默认的构建器。
they've got a  default web host builder you'll see here web host create default builder.
在很大程度上，
and for the most part,
我可以用这个来继续使用他
I can just use this and go on about my merry way
如果我想要进入并配置一些东西
if I do want to go in and configure things
我可以，你知道只要键入dot，然后我就可以开始了，
I can you know just type dot and then I can start,
你知道我可以进入这里我可以配置细节
you know I can go in here and I can configure specifics
关于工作原理，
about how things work,
但在大多数情况下，我可以从这个默认的web主机构建器开始
but for the most part I can start with this default  web host builder and
我已经很好了
I'm pretty set go
如果我想深入了解GitHub上AspNet Hosting仓库中还有什么其他内容
if I do want to dig into what else is available in the GitHub AspNet Hosting Repo
有一个示例，它有一些额外的主机配置。
there's a sample, which  has some additional hosting configurations.
所以
so
这里有一个例子，如果我想指出，
here's one where they show for instance if I want to point,
其他的url，如果我想说，
other URLs if I want to say,
我想让我的应用程序响应5001和5000
I want my application to respond to, you know  five thousand and five thousand one,
或者你知道，如果我想在https或其他东西上回应他。
or you know if I want to respond only to this on https or other things.
这是我如何进入这个领域的一个例子
this is an example of how I could go in and do that
我只是在做加法
so I'm just doing in adding
对WebHostBuilder进行额外的调用
and making additional calls to the WebHostBuilder
酷！
Cool!
再举一个例子。
and for an example taking this even further.
这是其中一个
this is one where there
它是添加额外的配置一的示例
it's a sample where it's doing all kinds of additional configuration
添加特定的配置步骤
adding in specific configuration steps
我们在做一些事情，比如使用一个特定的ContentRoot
we're doing things like using a specific ContentRoot
所以这个ContentRoot是我的www根文件夹指向的地方
so this the ContentRoot is where my www Root folder points to
好的
ok
我可以把它指向别的地方
and I could point this somewhere else
对的
right
这里我们要做一些额外的useurl，一个用于HTTP，另一个用于HTTPS。
Here we're doing some additional UseUrls one for HTTP and one for HTTPS.
你可以编码，你可以设置一个不同的开发环境，
You can encode, you could set a different development environment,
你知道的，只是不同的东西。
and you know it just all kinds of different things.
这里我们在这里配置服务。
so here we're configuring services in line here.
您的服务通常在Startu类中配置
your services are normally configured in a Startup class
但如果你看一下，
but if you look at it,
如果我们回到这里
if we go back over to it in here
当这个调用Startup
this when this calls use Startup
这是一种惯例，就像一个很好的方法来清理我的Programs.cs . 所有的代码都不在这里，
that's actually just a convention for like a nice way to clean up my Programs.cs so all the code isn't in there,
对，
right,
所以我可以在这里配置内联
so I really could configure inline here
如果我需要的话。
if I had to need to.
这是做这类事情的一个例子。
so this is an example of doing that sort of thing.
在这个例子中，他们使用的是一个假服务器这只是为了测试
so here in this example they're using a fake server and that's just for testing you know
他们运行的是本地的，还有其他的选项，比如这个HttpSys服务器。
they're they're running a local one there's other optionsthere's things like this HttpSys server.
对的
right
这是在windows http.sys内核模式驱动程序之上构建的
so that's built on top of the Http.Sys kernel mode driver  inside of Window
这将服务于网络互动的网络关注，
that will serve  web interactions web concerns from there,
很酷，能给你Windows网络服务的所有功能
very cool to give you all the power of Windows web serving
使用.NET构建的完全管理的新服务器
using a new server that's built with .NET completely managed
在你的AspNetCore应用中运行。
and running here inside of your AspNetCore app.
很酷。
cool.
总结一下我们目前所讲的内容，
so to summarize what we've covered so far,
我们有一个叫做Kestrel的NuGet包
we've got a NuGet package called Kestrel
我们将它导入到我们的应用程序中，它实际上只是一个控制台应用程序
we are pulling it into our application which really was just a console app
然后我们说。
and then we said.
导入这个新的git包
pull in this new git package
然后配置它，现在
and then configure it and now
我的控制台应用程序作为一个web服务器。
my console application as a web server.
非常整洁。
pretty neat.
现在我们有了这个，我们可以看一下
so now that we've got that we can look at
我们也要把它部署到这里。
where we are going to deploy this too.
就像我之前提到的
and as I mentioned before theirs
这些步骤，第一个是我们的主机设置
those steps to it, so number one we've got our host setup
还有一些其他的东西，现在我们想要把它放到上面运行
and then there are other things that， you know ，now we want to get this out onto them and run them
我们把它发布到一个文件夹。
so we publish to a folder.
如果我在visual studio中右键点击发布，或者我发布了像azure工具之类的东西。
and you know if I right click  publish in visual studio or if I publish  using that like the azure tools  etc.
很多东西都是为我处理的，但是我需要从命令行来做的就是键入dotnet publish
a lot of those things are kind of handled for me ，but all I need to do from command line is type dotnet publish
这就会发布我想要部署的代码。
and that's going to publish just the code that I'm going to want to deploy.
好吧
all right
所以
so
好了，在那之后对于不同的环境，有不同的步骤，我的程序是如何被监控的？
Alright. So after that there's kind of different steps for the different environments as far as， how my process is monitored?
反向代理是什么，它实际上是怎样的
and what the reverse proxy is， how it's actually how
网络服务器把什么东西喂给kestrel
what the web server is it's kind of feeding things into kestrel
对，反向代理就是前端
right so that reverse proxy is a front-end
像apache引擎Nginx或IIS这样的商业级web服务器
commercial-grade web server like apache engine Nginx or IIS
它会接收到这些初始请求。
that's going to receive those initial request.
也许它会处理这些SSL交互。
maybe it'll handle those SSL interactions.
任何其他的安全问题
any kind of other security concerns
然后回过头来把这个请求提交给kestrel
and then turn around and submit that request back  kestrel
就像人们在——
much the same way that folks in--
在节点环境中使用Express。
in the node environment use Express.
完全正确
exactly
然后你知道我的应用程序只关心http
and then you know my application is concerned with just serving http
所有这些更高层次的事情
and all those kind of other higher level things that I may want to do and
你知道
you know
就像你说的一个商业级的网络服务器，我可以在那里处理这些东西。
like you said a commercial-grade web server I can handle that stuff there.
所以当我们进行一些不同的部署时。
So as we kind of go through some of the  different options for deploying.
所以IIS，实际上这是一篇关于设置IIS的很长的文章
So IIS, there's actually this is a long article here about setting up IIS
这方面有相当多的步骤。
and there are  a decent amount of steps to this.
老实说，我喜欢把它部署到Azure中
which is one reason honestly, that I like deploy into Azure
因为我可以推到Azure让他们担心这个问题
because I can just push  Azure and let them worry about that
对你来说，他们把所有这些预定义的默认值作为你的最佳实践，
for you and they take all those predefined defaults the best practices for you,
是的
Yea
处理一些事情，比如windows更新
and handle things like you know,  windows update
必须说
just must say
但这些都是例子，这是通过设置IIS来遍历我
but so these are kind of the examples here ，this is walking through me through setting up IIS
有一个ASP NET Core,
There is an ASP NET Core,
所以这是。什么是.NET Core
so there's a-- what is it .NET Core
windows服务器托管包，这是一个exe文件
windows server hosting bundle. and this is an exe
这是我在服务器上安装的东西，我的web服务器
this is something that I would install on my server， my web server
它会为我配置一些东西
and it'll actually go through and configure things for me.
如果你在azure中设置一个vm或者你有一个on-prem服务器
so if you were setting up a vm in azure or if you had an on-prem server
你在配置IIS时也有.NET Core 主机
that you were configuring IIS on to also have .NET Core hosting
你可以使用.NET Core windows服务器托管包
you would use this .NET Core windows server hosting bundle
为了使用ASP.NET Core这些特性，我们需要一个网站，
to put down those features from ASP.NET Core we need  in order to host a website,
完全正确
exactly
这样方法在我安装后的IIS中它实际上是在使用这个ASP.NET Core模块。
So the way this is done and in IIS after I've installed  that is it's actually using this ASP.NET Core module.
ASP NET Cor模块实际上是为我做代理。
And the ASP NET Core module is actually doing this proxy for me.
所以如果我们看一下这里的互联网IIS就是前端，它实际上有一个正在运行的核心模块
so if we look at it here's theinternet IIS is that front end and it's actually got this  core module that it's running
这个核心模块正在返回我的应用程序。
and that core module is calling back into my application.
然后我们在这里看到的是我的应用程序它实际上是kestrel作为前端，它在我的应用程序代码中来回调用
and then as we see here here's my application and it's actually got kestrel as kind of the front end that's calling back and forth into my application code
酷！
Cool！
所以这很有趣当然，这就像我说的，这是安装在服务器上的
so yeah so this is really interesting and of course  this is like I said this is installed by that server install thing for me
这就为我设置了IIS。
So that will kind of set it up for me with IIS.
这就是它的工作原理，这是你要做的主要方式
so that's how it's done there， and that's kind of the main way that you're going to be doing this
不过，还有一些其他的选择。
There are some other options available though.
在Windows服务中有一个选择
There's the option to host in a Windows service
这很简洁。
which is pretty neat.
所以实际上有一个包，我可以安装它可以设置它。
so there's actually a package  that  I am,  I'm able to install that can set that up.
这是Microsoft.AspNet.Core.Hosting.WindowsServices包。
this is the Microsoft.AspNet.Core.Hosting.WindowsServices package.
如果我把它添加到我的应用程序中，
and so if I add that into my application here ，
你会看到这是，这是你知道的
so you'll see this is--  this is  you know
把它包含进来，这就开始的时候就很相似了
got that pulled in and then it's actually pretty similar on start
这里有一些东西，我们在这里是运行它最简单的情况
There's a few things, we're doing here we're saying the very simplest case is you basically run it
它被配置为一种服务
and it's it's configured as a service however
很多时候，我想要调试它，然后构建
a lot of the time I want to actually be able to debug it,  and build
就像我想要的那样——当我在开发我的应用程序时，我希望能够进入代码调试以及所有类似的东西。
you know， like I want it as I'm-- as I'm developing my application I want to be able to kind of  step into the code debug and all that kind of stuff.
这是文档中的推荐显示设置，它可以让它以双模式运行或者作为一个控制台应用
So kind of the recommended way and this is shown in the docs is to set it up where you can say allow it to run in dual mode either as a console app allow it to run in duel mode  either as a console app
或者作为一种服务。
or as a service.
好的
ok
这里配置的方式是说如果有一个调试器或者如果我传入命令行参数——控制台
So the way this is configured here this is saying  if a debugger is attached or if I pass in the command line arguments--console
然后设置为false。
then set this is service to false.
然后它的运行稍有不同，如果它说，
And then it runs slightly differently if it says it's，
如果它是一个服务那么它就会设置——为目录路径设置东西，目录路径是不同的
if it is a service then it kind of sets--  sets things for a directory path， the directory path is different
对吧？
right ?
然后还有这个
and then also there's this
host.RunAsCustomService，这是通过NuGet包所获得的。
host.RunAsCustomService so this is what's pulled in
via that new git package.
这是标准的kestrel运行
So this is the standard kestrel run
但是如果我们是作为服务运行的
and but if we're running if as service
而不是像定制服务那样运行。
than it does this run as custom service.
好的
ok
好的，然后注册的方式是使用这个SC命令
OK. And then the way that's registered is actually using this SC command
如果我们看一看，我在这里得到了这个，
So if we take  a look I've actually got this here,
跳转到文件夹然后我使用一个批处理文件来设置它
jump over into folder and I set this up  using a batch file
这里有几行代码。
and only because this is a few lines of code to type here.
如果我们看一下，这就是sc创建
so if we look, so this is sc create
这就是sc，它是一种注册服务
so that's sc is the-- the thing to kind of register a service
所以我说，sc创建服务的名称，然后是binPath。
so I say sc create the name of the service and then binPath.
有一件事是
and the one thing that's
这很有趣，我用.net发布了
that's a little interesting this binPath， I've actually used .net publish
在我的应用程序中，我从命令行中做了.net publish
so in my application I  from command-line I did dot net publish
然后我复制了exe被发布到的路径。
I-- and then I've copied that path where the exe was published to.
好的
ok
好的，现在我要使用这个服务我将以管理员的身份运行
OK. So now I'm going to take this service and I will do run as administrator
现在开始运行了
and that's now running
就像这样，因为它是注册为服务的。
that's like that cause it's registered as a service.
现在，如果我访问localhost：5,000，我最喜欢的本地主机端口。
and so now if I go to localhost 5,000,my favorite localhost port.
因此，他作为一个服务运行——一个Windows服务。
So there's my service running this isbeing hosted as a service a Windows Service.
所以Windows服务是在处理你知道的，让我的进程运行，处理启动/停止所有这些东西。
So the Windows Service is handling the you know, keeping my process running handling the
Start/Stop all that kind of stuff.
这很像我们如何使用WCF服务进行自包含的部署
So this is a lot like how we would do those self-contained deployments with WCF services
回去。
back in the past.
对，没错
yep, exactly
所以，如果我在互联网上公开一些东西，我通常会公开我将使用IIS。
So again if I'm exposing something out on the internet I would generally expose I would use IIS.
当然
Sure
但是 我需要在本地托管运行的服务公开一些本地内容，等等。
but for something that I need to host locally have a service that's running exposed some local content et cetera that's--
这就是我的设置的
that's kind of how I can set that up.
是的，那就是，这个示例是和这里的文档联系起来的。
So yeah and that's-- that sample is out that's actually linked to from the docs here.
好的，很简单，当你知道sc运行这个sc服务时，我真的很惊讶。
OK. So relatively straightforward， and that sc I was honestly kind of surprised when you know, did the sc running through this sc service add.
这就像sc创造一样
and it just kind of worked sc create
最后，你还会想要把它清理干净，删除它，这是一个sc删除
and then at the end also you'll want to go through and clean it up, remove it and that's there's an sc delete
要做到这一点，你可以停止然后删除它。
To do that you stop it and delete it.
这就是这些。
so that is those.
我还想讲另一件事。
so the one other thing I kind of wanted to touch on.
在开始时，有个更重要的问题我要指出。但这是托管在linux上的
and this is a bigger thing I'm just going to point you in the direction to get started but is hosting on linux
再次在Linux上托管，您正在配置整个web服务器
Hosting on Linux again,  you're configuring  an entire web server
你在设置你的进程监视器，你在做反向代理。
you're you're setting up your process monitor ，and you're doing your reverse proxy.
好的，
ok,
这里有几个步骤。
so there are several steps there.
我想指出的是
I just want to point out
我经历了这个，我想指出一些陷阱和重要的注意事项和一些技巧。
I ran through this and I just want to point out some gotchas and important things to be aware of. and also some tips.
我在这里做了一个，我创建了一个Ubuntu VM
so one has I went in and actually did this in the-- I created an Ubuntu VM
我在那台机器上做了我的开发，在配置它的时候，他实际上是云壳。
and I did--  I did my kind of development on that machine as far as kind of configuring it  ，actually is the cloud shell.
所以这个云壳
So this Cloud Shell you
你只要点击这里就可以打开。
you can just bring up by clicking here.
这个启动器终端窗口在底部。
And this kind of launches ， this little terminal window down at the bottom.
好的
okay
这就是我进行配置的地方，为了做到这一点，我ssh到这个盒子里
So that's actually where I did my configuration， in order to do that I-- I ssh into the box
所以我实际上只是复制
so I actually just you know  copy
在这个方向上，在如何做的过程中但是我ssh到这个盒子里
it's in the--in the directions as far as how to do it but I ssh into the box
然后他们会带你去安装
and then they walk you through installing
现在你可以安装完整的sdk了，
now you can install the full sdk,
但实际上我们推荐的是安装运行时
but actually what's recommended is to install just the runtime
当然，或者你不想在你的服务器上安装整个sdk，尽管你不需要它。
Sure or you don't want to install the whole sdk on your server though you don't need it.
而且，你想要一个轻量的安装。
And-- and you want to kind of have a light-tight install right.
所以当你去下载的时候
so when you go to the downloads
默认情况下它会指向你的sdk如果你点击运行时
and kind of the default  it's going to point you to is  sdk if you click on run time
然后你可以向下滚动，你可以看到linux上安装.NET Core包了
then you can scroll down and you can see here are linux installing  .NET Core on linux.
然后这里，请注意，你读了版本号，这是。NET核心1.1.4（LTS）。
and then here.  be careful that you read the Version Number. So this is .NET core 1.1.4 (LTS).
这是长期支持版
It's long term support right.
所以，如果你想要.NET Core 2.0 你要向下滚动到当前。
So, you actually do if you want .NET Core 2 you want to scroll down to current.
对于这些，这是，字面意思是sudo apt-get你知道，
And then for these it's-- it's literally just sudo apt-get you know,
你首先要考虑的是来源
you have to consider here the sources for at first
这些来源都是标准的
So those sources are these standard ones here
如果你去下载 .NET Core
So, if you go downloads .NET Core
然后你点击linux。
and then you click on linux.
你仍然需要确保无论你的环境是什么，你已经完成了你的apt-get。
You're still going to need to make sure that for whatever your environment is that，  you've done your apt-get.
你知道，你已经为apt-get配置了你的资源
You know to you like you've configured your sources for apt-get
对的
right
我浏览了一下，注册了微软的签名然后apt-get安装
So I went through and then you know. registered the Microsoft Signature you know go through  and then install-- install the app-get using
但是，当我运行这行代码时
However, when I got to this line here
在哪里，你可以运行整个SDK
where-- where you would run the entire SDK
这就是你安装那个运行时的地方
that's where instead you install that runtime
好的
okay
这是有道理的。
it makes sense.
是的
yeah
这就是部署的主要内容
so that's that's kind of the main thing as far as how you  deploy
显然，我建议使用连续的部署
obviously you know I recommend still deploying using continuous
使用一些类似于GitHub的部署或者类似的东西来配置它是一件很好的事情
integration using some sort of like deploy from GitHub or that kind of thing that's kind of nice to configure that
在开发过程中进行配置
to configure that When you're in development
如果你在Windows上开发，你可以做的一件好事，你可以在Windows上使用Bash Ubuntu。
one nice thing that you can do if you're developing on Windows you can actually use Bash Ubuntu on Windows.
我的机器上有.NET .NET cd
So . I went through and  you know locally did this on my machine you know .NET and I actually have .NET cd
所以我在这里做了。NET发布，发布，
and so I did through here .NET publish, publish,
它在一个子目录下，在 bin目录下，cd bin
so it's-- it's in a sub-directory off a bin, cd bin
然后在下面进行调试
and debug and then down underneath
它有几个级别但是有一个是已发布的目录
its several levels but there's a published directory
对的
right
以及如何在你的生产服务器上获取你的文件。
and then as far as how you get your files out on your production server.
我在开发中所做的是使用scp。
what I did locally in development is use scp.
文档中有关于如何做到这一点的信息。
there is information in the docs about how to do that.
所以基本上rp是递归的
and so basically rp is recursive
我看到他指向一个目录，从本地st scp目录到azure vm目录
I saw him pointing to a directory I'm st scp from this local directory to  my  my azure  vm directory
我刚刚创建了一个应用程序目录
and I just created an app directory and did
你知道scp只是复制到那个，是的，这是一种标准，你知道，部署或复制文件的方式。
you know scp just copy to that. Yeah, that's kind of a standard， you know, way to deploy or to copy files up.
一旦我有了这个，那就是我的应用程序运行在那个服务器上。
so once I had that in place then that's my applications running on that server.
好的，
ok,
然后运行它开始，然后命中你 DLL的名字
So then to actually run it start and hit  you know and then just the DLL name
对的
right
在那之后，尽管你还没做完，因为你必须要经历，
After that though you're not done because remember you've got to go through,
在这里做所有实际的主机步骤，
and do all the actual hosting steps in here so,
实际上，你的应用程序已经复制到那里了但是现在你需要进行监控了
you're actually just your application has copied up there but now you've got to have  your monitoring
您还需要处理反向代理。
and you also need to handle your reverse proxy.
所以我们现在不打算讲这些了，我只是
so we're not going to go through all that now I'm just
向你们展示了如何开始的基本知识以及如何得到它，
showing you kind of the basics of how to get started and how to get it,
让它运行
You know get it running
还有一个重要的考虑因素
and an important considerations you've got
当然
Sure
好的
okay
我们已经讲过了应用程序是如何托管的基础知识
so we have covered starting with the basics of how your application is hosted itself
kestrel是如何运行您的应用程序的，或者是在您的应用程序中启用HTTP服务
How kestrel is running your application or is enabling HTTP serving inside your application
对的
right
我们研究了如何配置如何设置不同的kestrel选项
and we looked at how you configure that how you can set up some of the different kestrel options
你已经有了默认的web主机构建器，但是你可以浏览并配置很多不同的东西，我们看了一些示例代码。
You've got your default web host builder to start with but you can go through and configure a lot of different things and we looked at some sample code for that.
在那之后，我们研究了我们如何部署到几个不同的宿主环境中所以我们看了IIS，
After that we looked at how we're deploying to a few different  hosting environments so we looked at IIS,
我们将本地托管作为一个windows服务，
we looked at hosting locally as a windows service,
我们研究了一些需要注意的事情，让我们意识到部署到Ubuntu上的事情。
we looked at some kind of things to be aware of for things to be aware of for  deploying to Ubuntu as well.
酷！
Cool!
好吧
all right
好了，我们在那里做了很多介绍，我学到了很多关于托管ASP.NET核心服务器的知识。
Alright! We covered a lot there, I learned a lot about hosting   an ASP.NET Core Servers.
非常感谢你的加入
thanks so much for joining us
我希望你们能跟上我们的ASP.NET Core系列的其他视频。
I hope you follow up with some of the other videos that we have in our ASP.NET Core Series for you.